Kobato. 21 TL
"…The Footsteps of Spring."
00 eyecatch}
"…Day of Farewell."
What the heck is this?
Hey, hey.
Who did you give your chocolate to, Kobato-chan?
Me?
Yeah!
I gave it to…
Sayaka-sensei, Ioryogi-san, Toshihiko-kun…
That’s not what I mean!
Who did you give your number one chocolate to?
Well, I like everyone, so…
Well, well?
Um…
Sorry to butt in on your fun, but…
Don’t get so worked up.
Could you call Sayaka over for me?
What did you come here for?
I’ve come to talk things over with her.
For the final time.
You can’t!
You won’t move, then?
I will not!
That’s a problem.
Kobato-chan.
It’s okay.
Let him through.
It’s been a while, Sayaka.
Please…
Just wait a little longer.
A little longer? For how long?
I think I’ve waited quite enough.
Why… did you change so much?
I didn’t change.
This is how I originally was.
You’re lying.
Just give it up already.
Are you trying to act tough because I’m here?
If that’s so, you’re going about this the wrong way.
You’re little more than a stranger to me, now.
That’s why you don’t have any
other choice, now that I’m here.
Or do you want the preschool to be
destroyed, right in front of the children?
You don’t have to be so obsessed with it.
Just start another preschool.
Fujimoto-san!
What’re you saying?!
You know it better than anyone!
Fujimoto-kun!
This preschool isn’t just some building!
It’s what she inherited from the late principal!
It’s really precious!
It can’t just be replaced!
If it’s not just a building, then
what are you trying to protect?
Are you saying this building is more important than the children?
If you’re fine with the children becoming victims, then stay.
But you should probably take a look at your priorities.
You…!
Don’t!
Laying a hand on me will probably just hasten the inevitable.
I understand.
I’ll close the preschool.
Sayaka-sensei?
In return, please wait until the graduation ceremony.
What are you doing, Dobato?
Hey.
Look here…
You’re getting the sheets wet right after they’ve dried.
Sorry.
Geez…
You’re giving us more work again.
Sorry!
I’m going to go to Okiura’s place.
And do what?
I’m going to ask him again to not tear down the preschool.
If you go, you’ll just make things more complicated.
But at this rate…
Just don’t go, okay?
Hey.
You…
Why did he suddenly show up?
What’s the point in asking now?
You’re threatening her.
If she wanted to, she could sue.
If she could, she would’ve done so long ago.
Besides…
She decided herself that she’d shut it down.
Quit the blabbing and just leave!
I won’t give up.
I’ll protect that preschool.
And how will you do that?
What an idiot, you don’t even know anything.
Wait!
We’re not done talking.
You act all cool, saying you’ll protect everyone.
If you think talking to me will do anything, you’ve got it all wrong.
Got it?
Our president was the one who had his eyes on the preschool in the first place.
President?
Okiura-san’s father.
The debt owed by Yomogi Preschool
was passed down from the previous principal.
That’s…
No…
The principal got caught up in those
money deals and died from the stress.
Knowing that…
…it’s as much that guy’s fault for doing whatever his father tells him to!
That’s why I’m saying you don’t know anything!
Don’t you know what would happen if the president actually got serious?
That’s why Okiura-san said he’d settle it himself.
I…
I believe Okiura-san took on the role of the villain
in order to protect the preschool from the president.
Even more so, I think he did it
to protect the woman he loved.
What kind of nonsense is that?!
You’re free to think whatever you like of it.
But…
Kobato, was it?
I owe her a favor.
That’s why we don’t want to
cause an uproar and hurt her!
Just do what Okiura says.
…top, we can see it as much as we’d like.
Let us search, let us search, for a new mystery.
All of the other preschools are full.
I’m on a waiting list myself.
I’m so sorry it’s come to this.
Here, eat up!
Wh-What’s this?
If you’d like, would you eat dinner with us?
You won’t be lonely if you eat with us!
Chise-chan…
U-Um, I appreciate the thought, but I can’t eat this…
That’s true.
No one would have an appetite at a time like this.
No, um…
I’m really happy that you thought of me.
Father, I’m sorry.
I couldn’t protect the preschool.
But even so…
…I still want to believe in him
somewhere deep down in my heart.
Quite the fool, aren’t I?
Chitose-san, I saw Okiura-san at the preschool today.
He looked really lonely.
I see…
He was the one who told us to leave…
Okiura-san probably still loves Sayaka.
And Sayaka still has feelings for him.
Then why is Okiura-san doing things to make her sad?
Even if people love each other…
Even if they treasure each other…
There are times when they have to go different ways.
That man!
If I follow him, I might find Okiura-san!
Hey.
Um!
Let me see Okiura-san!
Miss, just give it a rest.
Please!
It’s pointless even if you meet him.
Leave.
Wait!
Send her away.
Even if I do, I don’t think she’ll back off so easily.
Then leave her be.
She’s still there.
Okiura-san?
Every one of them… Why are they so taken in by that preschool?
Ioryogi-san, are you cold?
Of course I’m cold!
Why don’t you find an umbrella, or a place to take shelter from the rain?
Think a little!
But then if Okiura-san looks outside that window,
he won’t see that I’m here.
He won’t come out if you do this.
He’ll come out sometime.
If not today, then maybe tomorrow.
If not tomorrow, then maybe the next day.
How long are you planning to wait?
Until that man comes out, I’ll keep waiting.
How long are you going to be there?
Okiura-san!
Um…!
I’ve got nothing to speak with you about.
We’ll take down the preschool,
and the property value will go towards the debt payment.
That’ll settle everything.
I wanted to ask about something else.
I wanted to ask about how you really feel.
Like I said, the preschool is…
That’s not it!
What a troublesome girl.
Chitose-san said that…
…Okiura-san, you still have feelings for Sayaka-sensei.
And Sayaka-sensei still…
She still loves you.
I was wondering what you were going to say.
Okiura-san!
Okiura-san, if you still treasure Sayaka-sensei,
why are you doing such cruel things?
Even though we loved it…
Sayaka-sensei…
Me…
Fujimoto-san…
Everyone at Yomogi Preschool…
We all loved that place.
So…
I think you did it to protect Sayaka-sensei.
Even so…
You took Yomogi Preschool from Sayaka-sensei.
You made Sayaka-sensei sad.
I can’t think of you as a good person because of that.
But even if you aren’t a good person,
if you’re important to Sayaka-sensei…
Things can’t stay like this!
Please tell me!
In the end, our worlds were different.
I couldn’t hold back my father’s power.
That’s why this is the only way I can protect her.
You don’t hate Sayaka-sensei, right?
You still hold her precious, right?
Hey!
Sayaka-san.
Fujimoto-kun.
I couldn’t sleep.
You, too?
Sayaka-san.
He’s doing all the dirty work just to protect you.
Fujimoto-kun, what are you talking abo-
Okiura.
That’s…
B-But…
That doesn’t mean I can forgive him…
What’re you saying?!
If you don’t forgive him, the only thing he can do is disappear!
Are you okay with that?!
I… want you to be happy.
He’s the only one who can help.
That’s why you need to be with him.
But…
Thank goodness, you’re awake.
Sayaka-sensei.
You were standing for a long time in the rain?
In the end, everyone’s always been protecting me.
Kobato-chan, Fujimoto-kun…
And that man…
Where’s Okiura-san?
He just left.
Are you okay with things being this way?
Sayaka-sensei.
If you still think Okiura-san is precious to you…
Chase him down and hug him!
Hurry!
This won’t do…
Don’t forget your wish.